Sloop uh is a experimental estrogen
receptor
Agonist so people are abbreviating this
to Sloop which I think is hilarious um
it's a fantastic uh out of all the
research chemical S names I think rad
140 sounds pretty cool but I think Sloop
sounds better um so this is a uh now I
will completely preface this I am not
fully versed on this people have asked
me about this so I have looked into it
but I'm not an expert personally I'm not
really into the niche and novel
pharmaceutical research chemicals uh I
think both Stephen and I are actually
big Advocates of not taking experimental
drugs um I think that's a pretty good uh
pretty good rule to have because um if
it's not a life ore situation taking
something that's an unknown has when
we're looking at the risk to reward
equation the RIS risk of the unknown is
enormous if if you're healthy and you're
taking a experimental research compound
for the sake of putting on a bit of
muscle or dropping a bit of body fat I
don't recommend rolling that dice over
just doing the work of getting a little
bit more uncomfortable with training and
diet so Sloop uh is a experimental
estrogen receptor Agonist people are
saying some very interesting things
about what it does I've read the
research I believe there is currently I
don't want to get this wrong but I can't
say that I know exactly but there's less
than five studies on it all in rats I
believe there's two or three studies on
it in rats there's no studies on it in
humans and I don't even think there's
any long-term studies on it in rats so
it's an
experimental uh estrogen it seems to be
an estrogen analog or an estrogen
Agonist it hasn't been studed in humans
it does some interesting at the estrogen
receptor that we know about we have
absolutely no idea what this does in
humans we have absolutely no idea what
else this could do in humans I think
that from a lot of the research on other
estrogenic compounds that are not
bioidentical estrogen synthetic
estrogens we know that these things are
not good for things like cancer growth
so it's not something I would be messing
around with personally um I'm I'm just
also going to put this out there find
anyone online who's promoting this stuff
who isn't selling it that would be my uh
my
challenge exactly always be very careful
with um experimental drugs uh shorting a
few years ago there was a worldwide roll
out of some experimental Jabs I don't
remember exactly why they were but um
yeah don't mess with
those all right